{
  "exercises": [
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: I can play football",
      "answer": "ich kann fußball spielen"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: You (du) may eat pizza",
      "answer": "du darfst pizza essen"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: He wants to learn",
      "answer": "er will lernen"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: We must work",
      "answer": "wir müssen arbeiten"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: They should sleep",
      "answer": "sie sollen schlafen"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: I must drink water",
      "answer": "ich muss wasser trinken"
    },

    {
      "question": "Translate to German: I will play music",
      "answer": "ich werde musik spielen"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: You (du) will learn German",
      "answer": "du wirst deutsch lernen"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: He will eat bread",
      "answer": "er wird brot essen"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: We will drink tea",
      "answer": "wir werden tee trinken"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: They will go home",
      "answer": "sie werden nach hause gehen"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: I will sleep",
      "answer": "ich werde schlafen"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: She will read a book",
      "answer": "sie wird buch lesen"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: You (du) will write",
      "answer": "du wirst schreiben"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: We will speak English",
      "answer": "wir werden englisch sprechen"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: They will dance",
      "answer": "sie werden tanzen"
    }
  ]
}
